ticketscript.com 2016-05-05

# Privacy Policy - Ticketscript

**DATA COLLECTION**

**We collect personal and activity data, which may be linked.**  
We use technologies like cookies to identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address.

We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. With your explicit permission, we may also access other personal information on your device, such as your phone book, calendar or messages, in order to provide services to you. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Google and Facebook.

Our systems may associate this personal information with your activities in the course of providing service to you (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for).

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.

Our service does not currently recognize the “Do Not Track” signal that may be available in some web browsers.

**SHARING DATA**

**We may collect but do not share your location history.**  
To customize our service for you, we may collect and store your geographic location as part of your user profile. This data generally is not shared with others. We may ask for your consent on your first use of the service.

**We don’t share your personal data with other companies.**  
We generally do not share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with other companies, with the exception of advertising companies and analytics providers

**Advertising companies may collect data through our service.**  
Advertising companies may use and collect anonymous data about your interests to customize content and advertising here and in other sites and applications. Interest and location data may be linked to your device, but is not linked to your identity.

**You can ask privacy questions.**  
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us via [info@ticketscript.com](mailto:info@ticketscript.de).

**Analytics providers access data on our behalf.**  
Analytics companies like Google may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data.

Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so they can improve it. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors.[Privacy Policy and Choices](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245)

**DATA PROTECTION**

**We take detailed steps to protect personal information.**  
We take reasonable administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to safeguard and protect your information from unauthorized access or disclosure. This includes utilizing Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the personal information you input, and storing your information in encrypted form behind a firewall designed to block access from outside our network. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.

**YOUR DATA**

**You can ask privacy questions.**  
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us via [info@ticketscript.com](mailto:info@ticketscript.de).

**You can review more privacy-related information.**  
This privacy policy was last updated on December 1st, 2014. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, push notification or text.
